Manga
Club
Good work, you two.
I heard good things about your reading sessions.
Sounds like you've got the report ready, too.
No.
Sensei!
We're not submitting this report!
Do You Love Cosplay?
What are you talking about?
You have to submit something!
Senpai and I talked things over,
and we don't want to submit this.
Cool, these pictures came out good.
Not sure if this'll work,
but we'll at least be able to
put together a good report.
Ririsa?
Sorry! That sounds good.
Hey, Senpai?
Something's kind of bothering me.
Yeah... I think I'm feeling the same way.
Like, is this really what
we want to say we're doing?
I dunno.
I mean, we're basically lying to the school, right?
It's not technically wrong,
but it's definitely hiding the truth.
I love cosplay.
Is it really something
I need to hide from everyone?
Personally, I don't think you do, but I dunno...
But, like...
When we visited those kids at school,
being in cosplay felt so normal.
Y-you know,
I just figured we needed to do
something to grab their attention.
I didn't really think you'd take me up on the idea.
I just thought it would be a whole lot more fun for them.
Like, when you see someone in cosplay,
you look at them, right?
And it's not just us...
Cosplay grabs everyone's attention,
in a good way!
So why should we feel like we
need to hide it from people?
Senpai, you told me our passion defines us,
and that gives me the courage to show it.
You're right.
I see where you're coming from.
What about this club room, then?
Without a report, you won't be able to keep it!
You probably haven't heard of it,
but there's a pretty big
cosplay event next week.
There is?
What's at the end of May?
Oh, right, Yokosuka CosStream.
She's definitely heard of it.
Wait, you can't be serious!
We're going!
We're going to participate officially as a club,
and put that in our report!
Are you crazy?!
That's not going to convince
them you're a real club!
Why not?
Are you...
You have no idea how the outside
world judges people who cosplay!
So when are you gonna grow out of that?
How will you explain that to your husband or parents?
Look at that slut.
You just want attention.
Just submit that report and hide the less savory stuff.
Why bother being honest?
That'll save our club room,
but we'd be losing
something else in the process.
What, your pride? Come on...
Can I get your new ROM?
I'll take a full set!
Wow, we're gonna sell out before noon!
We should've made more!
This one was the best one yet.
Any hotter, and we'd have to
slap an "18+" sticker on it!
NEW RELEASE
SOLD OUT!
Hope this doesn't hurt my job hunt...
That's... Something we can worry about later.
Mayura, you going to Winter Comiket?
Of course I'm going!
I've got a cosplay I've spent a whole year making.
It's a masterpiece!
For real?! I can't wait to see it!
I heard you got an offer!
Congratulations!
You've been selected for the pool of incoming teachers.
Placement
HIGH SCHOOL HOME EC
Yeah.
You're finally gonna be a teacher!
Yeah, so I should probably...
Oh, but you're gonna show off your
masterpiece before then, right?
Huh?
It'll be your last Comiket as a student!
Uh... yeah. You're right.
Don't assume people will take you seriously
just because you're serious about it!
The world is a lot more complicated than that!
Okay, then what do you think about cosplay, Sensei?!
What? W-what do I think?
I always thought it was too
embarrassing to tell anyone about.
Even now, I feel a little embarrassed
to parade around saying it's what I do.
But, if anyone asks me who I am,
I'll tell them this:
I love manga. I love anime.
I love Liliel.
And I love sexy costumes.
I'm a cosplayer!
Whoa, Eri, she's way too young to be here!
Crap, we gotta stop her!
Hey, sweetie, how old are you?
This is a softcore event, so come back
when you're in high school, mmkay?
I wonder if she likes cosplay.
Maybe we'll see her around here someday.
Who knows...
But, it would be fun to see her again.
Sensei, the Manga Club makes, wears,
and takes photos of cosplay.
And we want to be taken seriously for it!
Maybe you're too young and naïve to realize the truth.
Or maybe I'm wrong.
"Why did I spend so much time on something
too embarrassing to talk about in public?"
"But if anyone asks me who I am, I'll tell them this:
"I can't if I want to live my life."
I love manga. I love anime.
"I can't wear it. I'm a teacher now."
I'm a cosplayer!"
You're so determined.
Huh?
"But it would be fun...
How could I...
...to see her again."
How could I not support you all the way?!
Sensei!
But you know what this means, right?
The Manga Club earned its club room
by doing well in big competitions.
A picture of you two having fun at a
cosplay event isn't going to cut it.
I'm the one who has to sign off
on the report for the principal.
You see where I'm going with this?
Fine, I'll spell it out for you.
You've gotta be the best!
You'd better be the most popular
cosplayer there, you got that?!
Y-yes, ma'am!
Can I get this, and this,
and three of each piece of Kai-sama
merch that came out today!
I-I'll get those for you.
Yay! You still had some left! Thank God!
We've got tons left.
The blue one's the least popular.
Oh, Kai-sama,
I'm going to fly up the rankings for you!
I'm going sky-high, my prince!
It's one of those cringe otaku...
How is she not embarrassed?
She's pretty cute, though...
You have a crush on a fictional character?
But you're so pretty.
I'm so sorry!
Yup! I don't like 3D boys!
Yokosuka CosStream?
Yes, we'll be there, of course!
That's nice to know.
But it's going to be a fierce battle, my friend.
Huh?
One of the Four Queens of cosplay, Nagomi,
will be working at an official industry booth!
Nagomi?
And she'll be a character
that went viral last week.
Her announcement got 100k retweets!
The fan area may be a ghost town, I'm afraid...
Steel your heart for battle!
Hi, everyone!
Hello!
How's the costume coming along?
You'd better be grabbing the accessories
I asked for last time!
Can we discuss the promo for that new game?
Can you talk while I do your makeup?
That's a lot of stuff.
Prince Charming
The Prince C summer merch dropped today,
so I went to Animate first thing this morning.
That early?
You could've gone next week,
and Kai's merch would still be available.
You wanna die, girlfriend?!
And it's Kai-sama, thank you!
I fell in love with a 2D boy.
Since that fateful day,
I've sworn off 3D men.
And if I want to be his perfect match...
...I'm gonna be the prettiest 2D girl in the world!
Heavenly Queen
Nagomi
Nice, Nagomi-chan! Love that smile!
Looks like this is it.
Yeah.
This one was pretty far away.
It's also a way bigger venue than the last one.
There's gonna be industry booths here, too!
Y-you kinda look more nervous than me!
Y-yeah, I wanna take really good pictures
we can put in our report!
It's not as fancy as a competition or anything,
but I bet if I can get some exciting pictures,
it'll more than make up for it!
I didn't get any pictures of you surrounded
by that huge crowd,
but if we can get another crowd going...
Y-you want me to do that again,
here, with way more people?
You, uh, okay?
S-senpai, could you say the magic words again?
Huh?
You know, when you said my Liliel was, uh...
You've got this!
Your Liliel is the cutest in the whole world!
Okay!
more embarrassing to
hear than she thought
say than he thought
I hope I'm not interrupting!
Magino-san!
Yoohoo!
I'm here, too!
As expected, it's very quiet over here.
We're in the right place, right?
There's already quite the line forming
outside the industry hall!
Everyone is here to see Miss 753, Nagomi!
I'll be Icola at CosStream!
See you there!!
That tracks,
as she's cosplaying character
that was all over social media last week.
She was hired by the company themselves
to wear a professionally-made costume,
a feat made possible only
because she is a professional cosplayer!
Today's battlefield is centered around Miss Nagomi.
Indeed, it already looks fierce.
I hope you came prepared.
'Tis always a tragedy when few
people come to see your costume.
Truly, no sorrow can compare.
Okay, we're gonna go change!
Roger-roger!
Come, friend, let us scope out the field!
O-okay!
Look, there's Nagomi-chan!
Ugh, Kai-sama's UR drop rate is 1.5%?!
Do they just want my whole bank account?!
I got a bunch of extra Kai cards, wanna trade?
Don't treat him like that! And it's Kai-sama!
And thank you!
All of them are Nagomi?!
No, she's the one in the middle!
The rest are from the company.
They're there to support their professional cosplayer.
A professional cosplayer... Wow.
Were you that Liliel?
Huh?!
I thought so.
My photographer showed
me the pic he got of you.
Hi. I didn't post it online, promise!
I barely recognized you here.
You still looked totally 3D, though.
You gotta work on your makeup.
R-really? I better study...
You doing Liliel again today?
Y-yeah!
U-um, what character are you cosplaying as today?
I dunno.
Huh?!
Sorry, who am I again?
Icola, from that new game.
You don't know her,
but you're still cosplaying her?
Yeah. She's not out yet,
so I wouldn't be able to know anything about her.
Pretty much every day I'm cosplaying
a character I don't know much about.
But I do it, 'cause I'm a pro.
Oh...
Look, I know what you're getting at.
It's not really cosplay if I don't love the character.
I'm just doing this to get famous.
I'm a sell-out.
"Pros" are just influencers forced to cosplay.
I've seen all that before in my comments and DMs.
Nothing I'm not already used to.
I-I wasn't thinking that at all, I swear!
There are tons of pros out there who pretend
they love the character so they don't get hate,
but I don't think we should even bother.
Wanna know why?
Because I love cosplay and cosplayers
more than anyone else out there.
When I'm in costume,
that's the only time I can transcend
this third dimension to 2D.
I never want to stop cosplaying.
That's why I do it professionally.
And I'm not just doing it for myself.
I want to wear the most incredible costumes,
and pose for cameras around the world.
I'm going to be the most perfect
2D girl the world has ever seen.
Kai-sama deserves the best, after all.
So that's why you'll cosplay characters
you don't know anything about?
That's right. I mean, think about it.
You love Liliel,
and cosplay is how you show that love.
I love cosplay, live for cosplay,
and show that all through cosplay.
So...
Which one of us loves cosplay more?
Hold on...
Here's some advice:
I'm going to be at the booth at noon,
so beginners like you shouldn't
bother going out there until this afternoon.
I-I'm so sorry.
Please don't take it personally!
She's not trying to be insulting,
she just gets intense about cosplay...
Hi, Liliel-chan!
I didn't think we'd see you till summer!
Yeah...
W-we're not bothering you, are we?
No, it's who we just ran into...
Whoa!
Damn, Nagomi started drama with you?!
I wouldn't call it drama.
I think I said something that made her mad.
Honey, she was absolutely trying to start drama.
But, she really knows her stuff!
I really wish I could've asked her some more questions.
Like, how does she get into character
when she doesn't know them that well?
She's so sweet...
She just needs confidence.
Yeah. I get why that's a downer,
but brighten up!
She's right!
You're gonna need the energy.
If you wanna survive the CosStream
changing room craziness, that is!
C'mon, focus up,
or there'll be no space left for your suitcase!
Yup! Cheer up, we're gonna have fun!
Okay.
I hope she's okay...
Izu-chan, hurry!
Make sure you don't forget anything!
Yeah, I'm going!
We're done here,
so you can spread out if you want!
Oh... Thank you.
We gotta get a spot before the industry hall opens!
Wait up!
Come now, milord Okumura!
I shall explain to you our plan of action.
Y-you already have a plan?
Why, of course!
Direct your attention to the map here.
Parking Lot Area
General Traffic Flow
Underground Walkway
Outdoor Photo Area
Hall A
Hall B
Regular attendees like ourselves are limited
to Hall A and the outdoor photo areas.
However, most attendees with tickets are
heading to Hall B for the industry booths.
So that means...
Yes, what we're fearing is that most attendees
will leave right after seeing Miss Nagomi.
If so, then they will head for the
exit nearest to the industry hall,
through this passageway.
That is where we will stake our claim!
Few cosplayers will station themselves there,
and everyone will need to pass by us!
If enough stop for pictures,
we will most certainly create a buzzing crowd!
T-that makes sense!
At worst, we can aim for the time period when
Miss Nagomi returns to her booth,
but we may need to prepare for
most attendees to leave when she does.
No matter!
Clash with the Heavenly Queens is inevitable
when aiming for the highest heights!
Let us go forth, milord Okumura!
O-okay!
We can do this, Ririsa!
"So...
Which one of us loves cosplay more?"
Cosplay Stream 55 will begin shortly!
You're Not Liliel!